Office of the Board of Trustees Records UA003
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office of the Board of Trustees Records
1848 -- 2020
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Trustees of Tufts College
Office of the Trustees
UA003
163.47 Linear Feet 158 boxes
3 Volumes
1 Artifact(s)
337 Digital Object(s) 337 digital objects containing approximately 14,413 files.
17.68 Gigabytes
This collection contains the records of the activities of the Board of Trustees beginning in 1848.
Conditions Governing Access
Records containing information related to student education, staff and faculty employment, and Board of Trustees records are closed for 75 years from the date of creation. This collection may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by the Board of Trustees, 2006 -- 2021.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into 21 series: Full Board, Executive Committee, Academic Affairs Committee, Administration and Finance Committee, Audit Committee, Honorary Degree Committee working papers and subject files, Committee on Trusteeship, University Advancement Committee, Compensation Committee, Subcommittee Buildings and Grounds, Subject Files, Board of Visitors Committee, Investment Committee, Compiled Subject Files, Artifacts and photographs, Office files, Trustees Weekend Working Papers and Minutes, Financial and Investment Records, Campaign Committees, Student Affairs Committee, and Unprocessed accessions.
Biographical / Historical
In 1851, a Board of Trustees was nominated by the subscribers to replace the temporary Board created at the 1847 Educational Convention of the Universalist Church. The new Board selected a site and drew up the governing rules for the new College.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the records of the activities of the Board of Trustees from 1848 on. The bulk of these materials are arranged in chronological order by the date on which the meeting occurred. The collection contains meeting announcements, agendas, minutes, memos, reports, clippings, photographs, correspondence, event records, budget materials, policies, strategic plans, degree lists, honorary degree files, and commencement programs. Files labeled "working papers" contain meeting announcements, agendas, minutes, letters, memos, and supplemental material (i.e., reports and newspaper and journal articles) related to the specific meeting. Although the earliest material in the collections dates to the founding of the college, working papers of the full board meetings and various committee meetings were not regularly kept until the fall of 1974.
Administration and Governance -- Governance; Administration and Governance -- Planning, evaluation, policies & procedures; Finance
- Full Board, 1851 -- 2020; UA003.001; 14.95 Linear Feet; 5 Volumes; 38 Digital Object(s) 38 zip files containing 670 files.; 1.83 Gigabytes
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains Tufts University's Full Board of Trustees documents from 1851 to the 2000. The bulk of these materials are arranged in chronological order by the date on which the meeting occurred. Folders contain meeting announcements, agendas, minutes, letters, memoranda, and supplemental material (i.e., reports and newspaper and journal articles).
  The Board has the authority to carry out all lawful functions permitted by the bylaws and include but are not limited to the following: reviewing and approving the university's mission and purposes; appointing the President; establishing the conditions of employment of key officers; supporting the President and assessing his performance; reviewing and approving proposed major changes in the academic programs; approving institutional policies bearing on faculty appointments; approving the annual budget; monitoring the university's financial condition; fundraising; authorizing debt financing and loans; authorizing construction; approving degrees; and reviewing board performance.
  Although the earliest material dates to the founding of the college, the working papers of the Full Board meetings were not regularly kept until the fall of 1974.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically by meeting date.
  Conditions Governing Access
  75 years from the date of creation. Open for research.
  - Working papers, 1958 -- 2012; UA003.001.001
    Open for research.
    - Full Board, 1958 -- 1963; UA003.001.016.00001 (Box 16)
      75 years from the date of creation.
    - Full Board, 1962 -- 1968; UA003.001.016.00002 (Box 16)
    - Full Board, 1969; UA003.001.016.00003 (Box 16)
    - Full Board December 12, 1970; UA003.001.016.00004 (Box 16)
    - Full Board March, June, October, 1971; UA003.001.016.00005 (Box 16)
    - Full Board October 29, 1971; UA003.001.016.00006 (Box 16)
    - Full Board April 28, 1972; UA003.001.016.00007 (Box 16)
    - Full Board June 14, 1974; UA003.001.016.00008 (Box 16)
    - Full Board November 2, 1974; UA003.001.016.00009 (Box 16)
    - Full Board February 1, 1975; UA003.001.016.00010 (Box 16)
    - Full Board May 24 [1/2], 1975; UA003.001.016.00011 (Box 16)
    - Full Board May 24 [2/2], 1975; UA003.001.016.00012 (Box 16)
    - Full Board June 14, 1975; UA003.001.016.00013 (Box 16)
    - Full Board, self-study, 1969; UA003.001.016.00014 (Box 16)
    - Full Board, November 1, 1975; UA003.001.017.00001 (Box UA003 Shared 1)
    - Full Board, November 1, 1975; UA003.001.017.00002 (Box UA003 Shared 1)
    - Full Board, November 24, 1975; UA003.001.017.00003 (Box UA003 Shared 1)
    - Full Board, February 14, 1976; UA003.001.017.00004 (Box UA003 Shared 1)
    - Full Board, March 20, 1976; UA003.001.017.00005 (Box UA003 Shared 1)
    - Full Board, May 22, 1976; UA003.001.017.00006 (Box UA003 Shared 1)
    - Full Board, May 22, 1976; UA003.001.017.00007 (Box UA003 Shared 1)
    - Full Board, May 22, 1976; UA003.001.017.00008 (Box UA003 Shared 1)
    - Full Board, October 30, 1976; UA003.001.018.00001 (Box 18)
    - Full Board, October 30, 1976; UA003.001.018.00002 (Box 18)
    - Full Board, February 5, 1977; UA003.001.018.00003 (Box 18)
    - Full Board, March 26, 1977; UA003.001.018.00004 (Box 18)
    - Full Board, May 21, 1977; UA003.001.018.00005 (Box 18)
    - Full Board, May 21, 1977; UA003.001.018.00006 (Box 18)
    - Full Board, November 4-5, 1977; UA003.001.018.00007 (Box 18)
    - Full Board, November 5, 1977; UA003.001.019.00001 (Box 19)
    - Full Board, (Spec. Mtg.) April 29, 1978; UA003.001.019.00003 (Box 19)
    - Full Board, May 20, 1978; UA003.001.019.00004 (Box 19)
    - Full Board, May 20, 1978; UA003.001.019.00005 (Box 19)
    - Full Board, May 20, 1978; UA003.001.019.00006 (Box 19)
    - Full Board, October 28, 1978; UA003.001.019.00007 (Box 19)
    - Full Board, October 28, 1978; UA003.001.019.00008 (Box 19)
    - Full Board, October 28, 1978; UA003.001.019.00009 (Box 19)
    - Full Board, October 28, 1978; UA003.001.020.00001 (Box 20)
    - Full Board, February 24, 1979; UA003.001.020.00002 (Box 20)
    - Full Board (Working Papers), May 19, 1979; UA003.001.020.00003 (Box 20)
    - Full Board, November 3, 1979; UA003.001.020.00004 (Box 20)
    - Full Board (Budget), 1979 -- 1980; UA003.001.020.00005 (Box 20)
    - Full Board (Mail Ballot), January 21, 1980; UA003.001.020.00006 (Box 20)
    - Full Board, February 23, 1980; UA003.001.020.00007 (Box 20)
    - Full Board (Intergrative Planning), 1980; UA003.001.020.00008 (Box 20)
    - Full Board, May 24, 1980; UA003.001.020.00009 (Box 20)
    - Full Board, October 31-November 1, 1980; UA003.001.020.00010 (Box 20)
    - Full Board, February 28, 1981; UA003.001.020.00011 (Box 20)
    - Full Board (Honorary Peabody Degreet Vote), April 15, 1981; UA003.001.021.00001 (Box 21)
    - Full Board, May 30, 1981; UA003.001.021.00002 (Box 21)
    - Full Board (Mail Ballot: Univ. Librarian), August, 1981; UA003.001.021.00003 (Box 21)
    - Full Board, October 23, 1981; UA003.001.021.00004 (Box 21)
    - Full Board, October 24, 1981; UA003.001.021.00005 (Box 21)
    - Full Board, February 27, 1982; UA003.001.021.00006 (Box 21)
    - Full Board, May 29, 1982; UA003.001.021.00007 (Box 21)
    - Full Board, November 5-November 6, 1982; UA003.001.021.00008 (Box 21)
    - Full Board, February 26, 1983; UA003.001.021.00009 (Box 21)
    - Full Board, May 28, 1983; UA003.001.021.00010 (Box 21)
    - Full Board, November 4, 1983; UA003.001.021.00011 (Box 21)
    - Full Board, February 25, 1984; UA003.001.021.00012 (Box 21)
    - Full Board, May 19, 1984; UA003.001.021.00013 (Box 21)
    - Full Board, November 2-3, 1984; UA003.001.022.00001 (Box 22)
    - Full Board, February 23, 1985; UA003.001.022.00002 (Box 22)
    - Full Board, May 18, 1985; UA003.001.022.00003 (Box 22)
    - Full Board, November 8-9, 1985; UA003.001.022.00005 (Box 22)
    - Full Board, November 8-9, 1985; UA003.001.022.00006 (Box 22)
    - Full Board, February 22, 1986; UA003.001.022.00007 (Box 22)
    - Full Board, May 17, 1986; UA003.001.022.00008 (Box 22)
    - Full Board, November 14-15, 1986; UA003.001.023.00001 (Box 23)
    - Full Board, November 14-15, 1986; UA003.001.023.00002 (Box 23)
    - Full Board, November 14-15, 1986; UA003.001.023.00003 (Box 23)
    - Full Board, November 14-15, 1986; UA003.001.023.00004 (Box 23)
    - Full Board, 1986 -- 1987; UA003.001.023.00005 (Box 23)
    - Full Board, February 28, 1987; UA003.001.023.00006 (Box 23)
    - Full Board, November 13-14, 1987; UA003.001.023.00007 (Box 23)
    - Full Board, November 13-14, 1987; UA003.001.023.00008 (Box 23)
    - Full Board, February 27, 1988; UA003.001.024.00001 (Box 24)
    - Full Board, May 21, 1988; UA003.001.024.00002 (Box 24)
    - Full Board, November 4-5, 1988; UA003.001.024.00003 (Box 24)
    - Full Board, November 4-5, 1988; UA003.001.024.00004 (Box 24)
    - Full Board, November 4-5, 1988; UA003.001.024.00005 (Box 24)
    - Full Board, February 25, 1989; UA003.001.024.00006 (Box 24)
    - Full Board, May 20, 1989; UA003.001.024.00007 (Box 24)
    - Full Board, November 3-4, 1989; UA003.001.024.00008 (Box 24)
    - Full Board, November 3-4, 1989; UA003.001.025.00001 (Box 25)
    - Full Board, February 24, 1990; UA003.001.025.00002 (Box 25)
    - Full Board, May 19, 1990; UA003.001.025.00003 (Box 25)
    - Full Board, November 2-3, 1990; UA003.001.025.00004 (Box 25)
    - Full Board, February 23, 1991; UA003.001.025.00005 (Box 25)
    - Full Board, February 23, 1991; UA003.001.025.00006 (Box 25)
    - Full Board, May 11, 1991; UA003.001.025.00007 (Box 25)
    - Full Board, November 2, 1991; UA003.001.025.00008 (Box 25)
    - Full Board, February 29, 1992; UA003.001.025.00009 (Box 25)
    - Full Board, May 16, 1992; UA003.001.025.00010 (Box 25)
    - Full Board, November 7, 1992; UA003.001.025.00011 (Box 25)
    - Full Board, February 27, 1993; UA003.001.026.00001 (Box 26)
    - Full Board, February 27, 1993; UA003.001.026.00002 (Box 26)
    - Full Board, May 22, 1993; UA003.001.026.00003 (Box 26)
    - Full Board, November 6, 1993; UA003.001.026.00004 (Box 26)
    - Full Board, November 6, 1993; UA003.001.026.00005 (Box 26)
    - Full Board, November 6, 1993; UA003.001.026.00006 (Box 26)
    - Full Board, November 6, 1993; UA003.001.026.00007 (Box 26)
    - Full Board, February 26, 1994; UA003.001.026.00008 (Box 26)
    - Full Board Working Papers, 1902 -- 1994; UA003.001.027.00001 (Box 27)
    - Full Board Working Papers, 1905 -- 1994; UA003.001.027.00002 (Box 27)
    - Full Board [Working Papers] [1 of 2], 1911 -- 1994; UA003.001.027.00003 (Box 27)
    - Full Board [Working Papers] [2 of 2], 1911 -- 1994; UA003.001.027.00004 (Box 27)
    - Full Board Working Papers, 1902 -- 1995; UA003.001.027.00005 (Box 27)
    - Board of Trustees [Working Papers], 1905 -- 1995; UA003.001.027.00006 (Box 27)
    - Full Board Working Papers, 1911 -- 1995; UA003.001.027.00007 (Box 27)
    - [Full Board Working Papers], 1903 -- 1999; UA003.001.027.00008 (Box 27)
    - [Full Board Working Papers], 1909 -- 1999; UA003.001.027.00009 (Box 27)
    - [Full Board Working Papers], 1910 -- 1999; UA003.001.027.00010 (Box 27)
    - [Full Board Working Papers], 2000 -- 2004; UA003.001.027.00011 (Box 27)
    - [Full Board Working Papers], 2000 -- 2009; UA003.001.027.00012 (Box 27)
    - [Full Board Working Papers], 2000 -- 2010; UA003.001.027.00013 (Box 27)
    - [Full Board Working Papers], 2000 -- 2012; UA003.001.027.00014 (Box 27)
    - February 11, 2000, part 1, UA003.001.084.00001 (Box UA003 Shared 2)
    - February 11, 2000, part 2, UA003.001.084.00002 (Box UA003 Shared 2)
    - April 6, 2000; UA003.001.084.00003 (Box UA003 Shared 2)
    - May 20, 2000; UA003.001.084.00004 (Box UA003 Shared 2)
    - September 11, 2000; UA003.001.084.00005 (Box UA003 Shared 2)
    - October 26, 2000; UA003.001.084.00006 (Box UA003 Shared 2)
    - November 4, 2000, part 1, UA003.001.084.00007 (Box UA003 Shared 2)
    - November 4, 2000, part 2, UA003.001.084.00008 (Box UA003 Shared 2)
    - December 2 and December 13, 2000; UA003.001.084.00009 (Box UA003 Shared 2)
    - Board of Trustees, 2007 -- 2010; UA003.001.124; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 124, Folder 22 - 34)
      Immediate Source of Acquisition
      Transferred by the Office of the Board of Trustees, 2018, accession UA-2019-011.
  - Degree lists, 1979 -- 2004; UA003.001.002
    - Degree List, May 19, 1979; UA003.001.082.00001 (Box 82)
    - Degree List, November 3, 1979; UA003.001.082.00002 (Box 82)
    - Degree List, May 24, 1980; UA003.001.082.00003 (Box 82)
    - Degree List, May 30, 1981; UA003.001.082.00004 (Box 82)
    - Degree List, October 24, 1981; UA003.001.082.00005 (Box 82)
    - Degree List, February 27, 1982; UA003.001.082.00006 (Box 82)
    - Degree List, May 3, 1982; UA003.001.082.00007 (Box 82)
    - Degree List, November 6, 1982; UA003.001.082.00008 (Box 82)
    - Degree List, February 26, 1983; UA003.001.082.00009 (Box 82)
    - Degree List, May 28, 1983; UA003.001.082.00010 (Box 82)
    - Degree List, November 5, 1983; UA003.001.082.00011 (Box 82)
    - Degree List, February 25, 1984; UA003.001.082.00012 (Box 82)
    - Degree List, May 19, 1984; UA003.001.082.00013 (Box 82)
    - Degree List, November 3, 1984; UA003.001.082.00014 (Box 82)
    - Degree List, February 23, 1985; UA003.001.082.00015 (Box 82)
    - Degree List, May 18, 1985; UA003.001.082.00016 (Box 82)
    - Degree List, November 9, 1985; UA003.001.082.00017 (Box 82)
    - Degree List, February 22, 1986; UA003.001.082.00018 (Box 82)
    - Degree List, May 17, 1986; UA003.001.082.00019 (Box 82)
    - Degree List, November 15, 1986; UA003.001.082.00020 (Box 82)
    - Degree List, February 27, 1987; UA003.001.082.00021 (Box 82)
    - Degree List, May 16, 1987; UA003.001.082.00022 (Box 82)
    - Degree List, November 14, 1987; UA003.001.082.00023 (Box 82)
    - Degree List, February 27, 1988; UA003.001.082.00024 (Box 82)
    - Degree List, May 22, 1988; UA003.001.082.00025 (Box 82)
    - Degree List, November 5, 1988; UA003.001.082.00026 (Box 82)
    - Degree List, February 25, 1989; UA003.001.082.00027 (Box 82)
    - Degree List, May 20, 1989; UA003.001.082.00028 (Box 82)
    - Degree List, November 4, 1989; UA003.001.082.00029 (Box 82)
    - Degree List, February 24, 1990; UA003.001.082.00030 (Box 82)
    - Degree List, May 19, 1990; UA003.001.082.00031 (Box 82)
    - Degree List, November 3, 1990; UA003.001.082.00032 (Box 82)
    - Degree List, February 23, 1991; UA003.001.082.00033 (Box 82)
    - Degree List, May 11, 1991; UA003.001.082.00034 (Box 82)
    - Degree List, February 29, 1992; UA003.001.082.00035 (Box 82)
    - Degree List, May 16, 1992; UA003.001.082.00036 (Box 82)
    - Degrees Voted, November, 1992; UA003.001.082.00037 (Box 82)
    - Degrees Voted, February, 1993; UA003.001.082.00038 (Box 82)
    - Degrees Voted, May, 1993; UA003.001.082.00039 (Box 82)
    - Degrees Voted, November, 1993; UA003.001.082.00040 (Box 82)
    - Degrees Voted, February, 1994; UA003.001.082.00041 (Box 82)
    - Degrees Voted, May, 1994; UA003.001.082.00042 (Box 82)
    - Degrees Voted, November, 1994; UA003.001.082.00043 (Box 82)
    - Degrees Voted, February, 1995; UA003.001.082.00044 (Box 82)
    - Degrees Voted, May, 1995; UA003.001.082.00045 (Box 82)
    - Degrees Voted, November, 1995; UA003.001.082.00046 (Box 82)
    - Degrees Voted, February, 1996; UA003.001.082.00047 (Box 82)
    - Degrees Voted, May, 1996; UA003.001.082.00048 (Box 82)
    - Degrees Voted, November, 1996; UA003.001.082.00049 (Box 82)
    - Degrees Voted, February, 1997; UA003.001.082.00050 (Box 82)
    - Degrees Voted, May, 1997; UA003.001.082.00051 (Box 82)
    - Degrees Voted, September, 1997; UA003.001.082.00052 (Box 82)
    - Degrees Voted, November, 1997; UA003.001.082.00053 (Box 82)
    - Degrees Voted, February, 1998; UA003.001.082.00054 (Box 82)
    - Degrees Voted, May, 1998; UA003.001.082.00055 (Box 82)
    - Degrees Voted, August, 1998; UA003.001.082.00056 (Box 82)
    - Degrees Voted, November, 1998; UA003.001.082.00057 (Box 82)
    - Degrees Voted, February, 1999; UA003.001.082.00058 (Box 82)
    - Degrees Voted, May, 1999; UA003.001.082.00059 (Box 82)
    - Degrees Voted, September, 1999; UA003.001.082.00060 (Box 82)
    - Degrees Voted, November, 1999; UA003.001.082.00061 (Box 82)
    - Degrees Voted, February, 2000; UA003.001.082.00062 (Box 82)
    - Degrees Voted, May, 2000; UA003.001.082.00063 (Box 82)
    - Degrees Voted, September, 2000; UA003.001.115.00001 (Box 115)
    - Degrees Voted, November, 2000; UA003.001.115.00002 (Box 115)
    - Degrees Voted, February, 2001; UA003.001.115.00003 (Box 115)
    - Degrees Voted, May, 2001; UA003.001.115.00004 (Box 115)
    - Degrees Voted, September, 2001; UA003.001.115.00005 (Box 115)
    - Degrees Voted, October, 2001; UA003.001.115.00006 (Box 115)
    - Degrees Voted, February, 2002; UA003.001.115.00007 (Box 115)
    - Degrees Voted, May, 2002; UA003.001.115.00008 (Box 115)
    - Degrees Voted, August-September, 2002; UA003.001.115.00009 (Box 115)
    - Degrees Voted, November, 2002; UA003.001.115.00010 (Box 115)
    - Degrees Voted, February, 2003; UA003.001.115.00011 (Box 115)
    - Degrees Voted, May, 2003; UA003.001.115.00012 (Box 115)
    - Degrees Voted, August-September, 2003; UA003.001.115.00013 (Box 115)
    - Degrees Voted, November, 2003; UA003.001.115.00014 (Box 115)
    - Degrees Voted, February, 2004; UA003.001.115.00015 (Box 115)
  - Meeting minutes, 1851 -- 1955; UA003.001.003
    - Minutes, 1851 -- 1857; UA003.001.086.00001 (Box 86)
    - Minutes, 1851 -- 1872; UA003.001.086.00002 (Box 86)
    - Minutes, 1872 -- 1878; UA003.001.086.00003 (Box 86)
    - Full Board, October 31, 1935; UA003.001.087.00001 (Box 87)
    - Full Board, December 9, 1935; UA003.001.087.00002 (Box 87)
    - Full Board, March 12, 1936; UA003.001.087.00003 (Box 87)
    - Full Board, June 13, 1936; UA003.001.087.00004 (Box 87)
    - Full Board, July 1, 1936; UA003.001.087.00005 (Box 87)
    - Full Board, October 29, 1936; UA003.001.087.00006 (Box 87)
    - Full Board, March 11, 1937; UA003.001.087.00007 (Box 87)
    - Full Board, April 2, 1937; UA003.001.087.00008 (Box 87)
    - Full Board, June 12, 1937; UA003.001.087.00009 (Box 87)
    - Full Board, July 2, 1937; UA003.001.087.00010 (Box 87)
    - Full Board, July 21, 1937; UA003.001.087.00011 (Box 87)
    - Full Board, September 8, 1937; UA003.001.087.00012 (Box 87)
    - Full Board, October 28, 1937; UA003.001.087.00013 (Box 87)
    - Full Board, November 12, 1937; UA003.001.087.00014 (Box 87)
    - Full Board, June 11, 1938; UA003.001.087.00015 (Box 87)
    - Full Board, September 16, 1938; UA003.001.087.00016 (Box 87)
    - Full Board, October 27, 1938; UA003.001.087.00017 (Box 87)
    - Full Board, March 9, 1939; UA003.001.087.00018 (Box 87)
    - Full Board, June 17, 1939; UA003.001.087.00019 (Box 87)
    - Annual Report of President to Board, October 26, 1939; UA003.001.087.00020 (Box 87)
    - Full Board, October 26, 1939; UA003.001.087.00021 (Box 87)
    - Full Board, March 14, 1940; UA003.001.087.00022 (Box 87)
    - Full Board, June 15, 1940; UA003.001.087.00023 (Box 87)
    - Full Board, October 31, 1940; UA003.001.087.00024 (Box 87)
    - Full Board, March 13, 1941; UA003.001.087.00025 (Box 87)
    - Full Board, June 14, 1941; UA003.001.087.00026 (Box 87)
    - Full Board, October 30, 1941; UA003.001.087.00027 (Box 87)
    - Full Board, June 19, 1948; UA003.001.087.00028 (Box 87)
    - Full Board, October 28, 1948; UA003.001.087.00029 (Box 87)
    - Full Board, March 10, 1949; UA003.001.087.00030 (Box 87)
    - Full Board, June 18, 1949; UA003.001.087.00031 (Box 87)
    - Full Board, October 27, 1949; UA003.001.087.00032 (Box 87)
    - Charter of Trustees, May 1, 1951; UA003.001.087.00033 (Box 87)
    - Full Board, monthly reports, September - December, 1889 -- 1891; UA003.001.104 (Box 104)
    - Full board minutes Volume 1, 1851 -- 1878; UA003.001.105.00001 (Box 105)
      September 16, 1851-January 16, 1878
    - Full board minutes Volume 3, 1887 -- 1895; UA003.001.106.00001 (Box 106)
      December 12, 1887-December 9, 1895
    - Full board minutes Volume 4, 1896 -- 1902; UA003.001.107.00001 (Box 107)
      March 9, 1896-June18, 1902
    - Full board minutes Volume 5, 1902 -- 1907; UA003.001.108.00001 (Box 108)
      August 27, 1902-March 12, 1907
    - Full board minutes Volume 6, 1907 -- 1910; UA003.001.109.00001 (Box 109)
      April 16, 1907- June 15, 1910
    - Full board minutes Volume 2, 1878 -- 1887; UA003.001.110.00001 (Box 110)
      May 21, 1878-November 15, 1887
    - Full board minutes Volume 7, 1910 -- 1916; UA003.001.110.00002 (Box 110)
      October 11, 1910-June 21, 1916
    - Full board minutes Volume 8, 1916 -- 1922; UA003.001.110.00003 (Box 110)
      October 16, 1916-April 12, 1922
    - Full board minutes Volume 9, 1922 -- 1925; UA003.001.110.00004 (Box 110)
      June 15 1922-December 10, 1925
    - Full board minutes Volume 10, 1926 -- 1930; UA003.001.110.00005 (Box 110)
      March 11, 1926-June 14, 1930
    - Full board minutes Volume 11, 1930 -- 1933; UA003.001.110.00006 (Box 110)
      October 30, 1930-June 17, 1933
    - Full board minutes Volume 12, 1933 -- 1936; UA003.001.111.00001 (Box 111)
      October 26, 1933- July 1, 1936
    - Full board minutes Volume 13, 1936 -- 1939; UA003.001.111.00002 (Box 111)
      October 29, 1936-June 17, 1939
    - Full board minutes Volume 14, 1939 -- 1942; UA003.001.111.00003 (Box 111)
      October 26, 1939-October 29, 1942
    - Full board minutes Volume 15, 1943 -- 1946; UA003.001.111.00004 (Box 111)
      January 26, 1943-June 15, 1946
    - Full board minutes Volume 16, 1946 -- 1949; UA003.001.111.00005 (Box 111)
      October 31, 1946-June 18, 1949
    - Full board minutes Volume 17, 1949 -- 1952; UA003.001.112.00001 (Box UA003 Shared 3)
      October 27, 1949-June 7, 1952
    - Full board minutes Volume 18, 1952 -- 1955; UA003.001.112.00002 (Box UA003 Shared 3)
      October 10, 1952-January 20, 1955
  - Secretary's files, 1855 -- 1921; UA003.001.004
    - Board of Trustees, Secretary's Files (1 of 2 with index), 1855 -- 1896; UA003.001.101.00001 (Box 101)
    - Board of Trustees, Secretary's Files (2 of 2), 1855 -- 1896; UA003.001.101.00002 (Box 101)
    - Full Board, Secretary's Files, 1 of 3 (plus index), 1892 -- 1898; UA003.001.101.00003 (Box 101)
      Index only covers first 58 sheets in this folder (dated October 5, 1894). Not all items in chronological order.
    - Full Board, Secretary's Files, 2 of 3, 1892 -- 1898; UA003.001.101.00004 (Box 101)
    - Full Board, Secretary's Files, 3 of 3, 1892 -- 1898; UA003.001.101.00005 (Box 101)
    - Full Board, Secretary's Files, 1 of 3 (plus index), 1899 -- 1902; UA003.001.101.00006 (Box 101)
    - Full Board, Secretary's Files, 2 of 3, 1899 -- 1902; UA003.001.101.00007 (Box 101)
    - Full Board, Secretary's Files, 3 of 3, 1899 -- 1902; UA003.001.101.00008 (Box 101)